<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<beans xmlns="http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans" xmlns:context="http://www.springframework.org/schema/context" xmlns:p="http://www.springframework.org/schema/p" xmlns:mvc="http://www.springframework.org/schema/mvc" xmlns:util="http://www.springframework.org/schema/util" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans 
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans/spring-beans-3.2.xsd
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/context 
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/context/spring-context-3.2.xsd
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/mvc
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/mvc/spring-mvc-3.2.xsd
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/util
		http://www.springframework.org/schema/util/spring-util-3.2.xsd">
 
	<!-- =================================================================================== -->
	<!-- **** SPRINGIFIED TEAM MEMBER REFERENCE DATA									**** -->
	<!-- =================================================================================== -->

	<bean name="teamMembers" class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMembers">
		<property name="partnerGroups">
			<list>
				<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.PartnerGroup">
					<property name="partnerName" value="University College Cork, Ireland" />
					<property name="teamMembers">
						<list>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Ciara Heavin" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc BIS
																		&lt;br&gt;MSc MIS by Research &#45; The History of Ireland&#39;s Software Industry
																		&lt;br&gt;PhD &#39;An Investigation of Approaches to Knowledge Management in Small to 
																		Medium Sized Software Enterprises (SMEs)
																		&lt;br&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#45; From Knowledge 
																		Activities to Knowledge Scenarios&#39;" />
								<property name="role" value="Co&#45;Principal Investigator Supporting LIFE" />
								<property name="bio" value="Dr Ciara Heavin is a college lecturer and a senior researcher in Business Information Systems
															and co-director of the BSc Business Information Systems, UCC. She lectures systems analysis 
															and design, web development (HTML 5.0, CSS, JavaScript and PHP), data modelling, database development
															and opportunity assessment and recognition in high technology firms. Research interests include 
															the development of ICT industries, primarily focusing on Ireland's software industry specifically 
															investigating knowledge management (KM) in software SMEs. More recently, she has undertaken funded 
															research in the investigation, development and implementation of innovative technology solutions in 
															Healthcare systems. Reviewer for a number of top journals and conferences and a member of three 
															conference organising committees, Ciara is Managing Editor of the Journal of Decision Systems since 
															November 2011." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="https://www.linkedin.com/pub/ciara-heavin/46/153/3b7" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="http://research.ucc.ie/profiles/B004/cheavin" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/CH.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Joe Gallagher"/>
								<property name="qualifications" value="" />
								<property name="role" value="" />
								<property name="bio" value="to be added..." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="false"/>
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false"/>
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false"/>					
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Yvonne O' Connor" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc, PhD (Business Information Systems)" />
								<property name="role" value="IS Post-Doctoral Researcher" />
								<property name="bio" value="Currently, Dr O' Connor is an Information Systems post-doctoral researcher 
															on the FP7 Supporting LIFE project within the Health Information Systems 
															Research Center (HISRC), Business Information Systems at University College Cork. 
															The Supporting LIFE project explores the potential of mobile health use in developing 
															countries by community health workers. In particular, her research focuses on (a) 
															community health workers' decision making processes and (b) health-related outcomes 
															associated with a decision support system; namely, electronic community case management. 
															Outside of research, Yvonne is currently lead User Interface (UI) analyst for the 
															Supporting LIFE project. This work involves prototyping and designing graphic user interfaces 
															(GUIs) for both the Supporting LIFE application and website" />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true"/>
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true"/>
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="true"/>					
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="https://www.linkedin.com/in/yvonneoconnorbis/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="http://research.ucc.ie/profiles/B004/yoconnor" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/YOC.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Timothy O' Sullivan" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc, MSc, MBA, PhD" />
								<property name="role" value="Senior Software Engineer" />
								<property name="bio" value="Dr. Timothy O' Sullivan is the Senior Software Engineer 
															on the FP7 Supporting Life project. His research interests 
															include context-aware systems, mobile computing, agent-based 
															systems, and cloud computing. He received a BSc in Computer 
															Science from Cork Institute of Technology in 1999, an MSc in 
															Computer Networks in 2001 and a PhD in Computer Science in 2005, 
															both from University College Cork, Ireland. In 2011, he received 
															an MBA in Engineering Management from Manchester Business School, 
															University of Manchester, UK. He has published in a number of 
															national and international journals and conference proceedings. 
															Timothy has over ten years industrial experience working in senior 
															engineering and team leading roles in the fields of investment 
															banking, industrial automation, and telecommunications." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true"/>
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true"/>
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false"/>
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="https://www.linkedin.com/in/osullivantimothyj" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/TOS.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Siobhan O' Connor"/>
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc (Nursing)&lt;br&gt;
																	   BSc (Business Information Systems)" />
								<property name="role" value="Researcher" />
								<property name="bio" value="Siobhan O'Connor is a researcher on the FP7 Supporting LIFE project. She is a Registered General 
															Nurse (RGN), with a background in informatics. She received a first class honours B.Sc. Nursing 
															from University College Cork in 2013 and an honours B.Sc. Business Information Systems degree 
															from University College Cork in 2004. She spent several years working in the international 
															financial services industry before refocusing her career to healthcare. She is currently 
															undertaking doctoral studies at the University of Glasgow and her PhD research is focusing 
															on the implementation of public engagement strategies to recruit patients and their carer 
															to digital health and wellbeing technologies and services. She has won several awards for 
															her innovative use of mobile technology in nursing education and practice and has published 
															in a number of national and international journals and conferences. She is a member of the 
															Health Informatics Society of Ireland (HISI), the American Nursing Informatics Association 
															(ANIA) and the British Computer Society (BCS)." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true"/>
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false"/>
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false"/>					
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/SOC.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Deirdre Ryan"/>
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc, MPH, MSc" />
								<property name="role" value="Research Assistant / Project Administrator" />
								<property name="bio" value="Deirdre joined the UCC Health Information Systems Research Centre in February 
															2014 as a Research Assistant and additionally became Project Co-ordinator of 
															the Malawi e-Health Research Institute in May 2014. She is research and 
															administrative assistant for Supporting LIFE from September 2014.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
															
															She received a degree in Public Health &amp; Health Promotion from University College Cork 
															in 2009, and a Master of Public Health from the University of Glasgow. After graduating 
															from Glasgow in 2010, Deirdre went on to work with Scottish HIV Charity - Waverley Care 
															in Edinburgh, of which a period of time was spent working for the charity with Malawian 
															prisoners in Lilongwe. She has research experience having worked on an evaluation of BreastCheck - 
															Ireland's breast cancer screening programme, and also works as a health promotion officer for 
															UCC's Health Matters initiative. She most recently completed a Masters in Management with 
															the Institute of Public Administration in August 2014." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true"/>
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false"/>
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false"/>					
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/DR.jpg" />
							</bean>
						</list>
					</property>
				</bean>
				<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.PartnerGroup">
					<property name="partnerName" value="University of Washington, United States" />
					<property name="teamMembers">
						<list>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Prof Matthew Thompson" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc, MBChB, DTM&amp;H, DPhil, MRCGP" />
								<property name="role" value="Helen D. Cohen endowed Professor of Family Medicine and Vice Chair for Research at the University of Washington, Seattle" />
								<property name="bio" value="Matthew currently holds the position of the Helen D. Cohen endowed Professor of 
															Family Medicine and Vice Chair for Research at the University of Washington, Seattle. 
															He is also a part-time Family Doctor and has worked clinically in the UK, Africa, and the USA.
															Matthew's research is centred on improving diagnosis of children with infections in primary care 
															settings, as well as better management of non-communicable diseases in adults, through the use of 
															technological innovation and development of new diagnostic tools.  He has expertise in qualitative 
															research, observational studies, randomized/non-randomized controlled designs and systematic reviews.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
															
															He has led the development of new standards for using vital signs and clinical prediction rules in children 
															to identify those with serious illnesses, including meningococcal disease.  His other major area of work is 
															improving the diagnosis and treatment of children and adults with respiratory tract infections to enable GPs 
															to better discriminate between those presenting with self-limiting illness and those with serious respiratory 
															infection who would benefit from antibiotics.  In conjunction with these areas of work, he is evaluating the 
															role of new diagnostic technologies in primary care settings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
															
															He has over 150 publications in peer-reviewed journals, many of which are in the world's leading journals. He 
															has been directly involved in evidence syntheses and guideline development for the National Institute of Health 
															and Clinical Excellence (NICE), Cochrane Collaboration and the United States Preventative Services Task Force"/>
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/MT.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Victoria Hardy" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc, MSc" />
								<property name="role" value="Researcher at the University of Oxford" />
								<property name="bio" value="Victoria has varied research interests, but her work to date has predominantly 
															involved coordinating and managing clinical studies in both primary and secondary care.  
															Victoria led the recruitment of a randomized controlled trial investigating the 
															effectiveness of Brief Interventions for reducing alcohol consumption in hazardous 
															and harmful alcohol users, admitted to a hospital in Glasgow. She has recently coordinated 
															recruitment of 2,000 children across central England for a research programme seeking to 
															develop and validate a clinical prediction rule to enable GPs to better identify children 
															with serious infections who would benefit from antibiotics. She also managed recruitment 
															of 600 adults to the 3Cplus study investigating the association between colonization and 
															commensal carriage of respiratory pathogens and patient's self-reported symptom severity 
															and fever as well as the subsequent development of complications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
															
															She is currently undertaking two systematic reviews evaluating the diagnostic accuracy of 
															vital signs in predicting serious infection in children under five." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="https://www.linkedin.com/pub/victoria-hardy/89/58/66a" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/VH.jpg" />
							</bean>
						</list>
					</property>
				</bean>
				<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.PartnerGroup">
					<property name="partnerName" value="Imperial College London, United Kingdom" />
					<property name="teamMembers">
						<list>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr John O' Donoghue" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc, MSc, PhD" />
								<property name="role" value="Principal Investigator Supporting LIFE" />
								<property name="bio" value="Dr John O'Donoghue is a Senior Lecturer in eHealth at Imperial College London 
															and Deputy Director of its Global eHealth Unit. 
															He received his B.Sc. in Computer Science and a research M.Sc. in Real-Time Systems and 
															Simulation from the Department of Mathematics and Computing, Cork Institute of Technology, 
															Ireland and a PhD from the Department of Computer Science at University College Cork, Ireland. 
															He has published in a number of national\international journals and conference proceedings in the 
															area of eHealth and mhealth for both developed and developing countries. His main research areas 
															include: Pervasive Data Management, Quality of Data, Health Informatics and Medical based Information Systems. 
															For his doctoral research, he received the Massachusetts Institute of Technology 
															Ballou/Pazer DQ/IQ Research Award, which recognises a PhD dissertation that demonstrates a significant 
															contribution to the field of Information Quality (IQ).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
															
															The Global eHealth Unit is an international research hub for innovation and entrepreneurship in health 
															care. It is a multidisciplinary team, collaborating on a number of local, national and international 
															activities. It rigorous approach to research and development work provides a strong evidence base for 
															influencing policy and improving health education and practice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
															
															Examples of projects which John is currently involved with include, detection and management 
															of acutely ill patients on hospital wards, data management modelling for clinical trials, use of 
															mHealth technology to identify illness in children in developing countries, and development of systems 
															for integrated chronic disease management." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="https://uk.linkedin.com/pub/john-o-donoghue/7a/412/759" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/JOD.jpg" />
							</bean>
						</list>
					</property>
				</bean>
				<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.PartnerGroup">
					<property name="partnerName" value="Malawi Partners" />
					<property name="teamMembers">
						<list>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Joseph Wu" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc in Public Health&lt;br&gt;
																	   MSc in Epidemiology&lt;br&gt;
																	   Major in health informatics, disease surveillance" />
								<property name="role" value="Country representative for Luke International in Malawi&lt;br&gt;
															Acting regional representative for Luke International in Southern Africa"/>
								<property name="bio" value="Joseph Wu graduated from National Taiwan University with Master degree and majored in Epidemiology in 2006. 
															He is one of the pioneering researchers to assist Taiwan to develop the nationwide syndromic surveillance 
															system during the post-SARS period. He is the Program Manager of the Department of Overseas Service in 
															Pingtung Christian Hospital in Taiwan since 2008, Malawi Country Representative since 2008 and the Acting 
															Regional Representative of Luke International in Southern Africa since 2013. He is also a lecture in Mzuzu 
															University since 2009.&lt;br&gt;
															His research domain is diseases surveillance system and public health system strengthening through technology. 
															He is leading an integrated capacity building program of health informatics in Malawi (iCBP-him) funded by the 
															Royal Norwegian Embassy and the LIN's team of the Supporting LIFE project."/>
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/JW.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Jenny Hsieh" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="Bachelor of Science in Public Health" />
								<property name="role" value="Research Associate for Luke International in Malawi" />
								<property name="bio" value="Jenny Hsieh graduated from National Taiwan University with Bachelor of Science in Public Health. 
															She joined Luke International in 2013. Her major duties include coordinating implementation and 
															research activities for Luke International and the Supporting LIFE project in Malawi, supervising 
															student research and liaising with different partners. She is also a lecturer in Mzuzu University, 
															lecturing Epidemiology and Research Methodology at the Biomedical Sciences Department. She is 
															passionate about connecting research with program implementation." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/JH.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Rebecca Mtegha" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="Business Administration qualifications majoring in Management" />
								<property name="role" value="Project Coordinator Luke International in Malawi" />
								<property name="bio" value="Rebecca W Mtegha is the Administrator and Project Coordinator for various projects at Luke International Malawi. 
															Rebecca joined the organization in 2009 just as it was being registered with the government of Malawi. Major duties 
															involve administering the office, active communication and coordination between various projects, managing staff relations, 
															reporting to different stakeholders and other notable duties. Rebecca can handle multitasking and able to deliver results at a 
															set timeframe. Rebecca has innovative and analytical skills which Rebecca has developed during her tenure at Luke International 
															and a stint at educational institutions. Rebecca is currently based in Mzuzu, Malawi. Rebecca holds Business Administration 
															qualifications majoring in Management." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/RM.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dominic Nyirongo" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc in Agriculture&lt;br&gt;
																	   MSc in Strategic Management" />
								<property name="role" value="Work Pack leader Supporting Life &amp; Executive Secretary Ungweru" />
								<property name="bio" value="Mr. Dominic Nyirongo is the Work Pack leader and LEAR on the FP7 
															Supporting LIFE Project at Ungweru. Dominic is also the Executive Secretary 
															for Ungweru. His interests are in bringing positive change in the lives of the rural poor. 
															He graduated from University of Malawi, Bunda College of Agriculture with a BSc in Agriculture 
															(Rural development and Extension). He received an MSc in Strategic Management from 
															University of Derby in UK. Dominic has over 12 years experience in rural and community 
															development and in project management." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="/testurl/" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Nathaniel Chimbatata" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="" />
								<property name="role" value="" />
								<property name="bio" value="to be added..." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/NC.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Tiwonge Kawonga" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="BSc Electrical Engineering&lt;br&gt;
																	   MSc Electrical Engineering " />
								<property name="role" value="Researcher" />
								<property name="bio" value="Tiwonge Kawonga is a lecturer in ICT department at Mzuzu University. 
															He has a Bsc. in electrical engineering (University of Malawi) and Msc. 
															in electrical engineering (Wits University). He has published conference 
															papers in use of middleware in provisioning of distributed applications 
															and resource provisioning in optical networks. His current research interests 
															are in the performance of wireless networks, wireless sensor networks, development 
															of mobile applications for developing countries' problems and security in wireless 
															and distributed application environment. He is a member of supporting Life project 
															from the ICT department of Mzuzu University." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="/testurl/" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Baxter Griphin Chirambo" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="" />
								<property name="role" value="" />
								<property name="bio" value="to be added..." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/GBC.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Emmanuel Ngalande" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="" />
								<property name="role" value="" />
								<property name="bio" value="to be added..." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="/testurl/" />
							</bean>	
						</list>
					</property>
				</bean>
				<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.PartnerGroup">
					<property name="partnerName" value="Accelopment, Switzerland" />
					<property name="teamMembers">
						<list>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Jeanette Muller" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="MSc and PhD in Human Geography with a focus on European funding schemes
																	   &lt;br&gt;Several certificates for training courses (e.g. project management, medical device consultant)" />
								<property name="role" value="(Administrative) Project Manager; WP6 and WP7 participant" />
								<property name="bio" value="Dr Jeanette Mueller is founder and CEO of accelopment. She has over 20 years of experience in the acquisition and management 
															of publicly funded projects (IT, life sciences, social sciences and renewable energies) and has specialised in R&amp;D and 
															innovation projects. Thanks to several executive positions in IT, other companies and her own enterprises, Jeanette knows 
															how to organise projects efficiently and to serve different stakeholders. After graduating in Economic Geography at the 
															University of Bayreuth (Germany) and the Université de Perpignan (France), Jeanette acquired her PhD at the University of 
															Wales Aberystwyth (UK) in the field of European funding programmes." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="http://ch.linkedin.com/pub/jeanette-muller/5/616/79a " />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="http://www.jeanette-mueller.ch/ " />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/JM.jpg" />
							</bean>
						</list>
					</property>
				</bean>
				<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.PartnerGroup">
					<property name="partnerName" value="Lund University, Sweden" />
					<property name="teamMembers">
						<list>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Prof Sven Carlsson" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="Professor (PhD)" />
								<property name="role" value="Researcher" />
								<property name="bio" value="Sven Carlsson is Professor of Informatics at Lund University School of Economics 
															and Management (LUSEM). His current research interests include: the use of ICT/IS to 
															support management processes, business intelligence, knowledge management, enterprise systems, 
															technochange, IT management and governance, design and redesign of e-business, and 
															health information systems. He has a keen interest in the use of critical realism 
															in IS research and IS design science research. He has published more than 150 
															peer-reviewed journal articles, book chapters, and conference papers and his work 
															has appeared in journals like Journal of Management Information Systems, 
															Decision Sciences, Information Systems Journal, and Information &amp; Management. 
															Carlsson is a regional editor for Knowledge Management Research and Practice 
															(he is a co-founder of the journal)." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/SC.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Bo Andersson" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="PhD (Informatics)" />
								<property name="role" value="Researcher" />
								<property name="bio" value="Bo Andersson is a senior lecturer at Lund University and holds a PhD in Informatics. 
															He is conducting research within the mobility domain, from development to use. Areas 
															of special interest are mobile payment solutions and mobile applications for organizational 
															use. He also teaches requirements engineering and modeling at Lund University. 
															He is the former CTO of 21st Century Mobile Solutions, a development company in Sweden. " />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="https://www.linkedin.com/in/boander" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="http://www.ics.lu.se/staff/bo.andersson" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/BA.jpg" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Odd Steen" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="" />
								<property name="role" value="" />
								<property name="bio" value="to be added..." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="/testurl/" />
							</bean>
							<bean class="ie.ucc.bis.supportinglife.reference.TeamMember">
								<property name="name" value="Dr Nicklas Holmberg" />
								<property name="qualifications" value="" />
								<property name="role" value="" />
								<property name="bio" value="to be added..." />
								<property name="photoPresent" value="true" />
								<property name="linkedInProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="researchProfilePresent" value="false" />
								<property name="linkedInUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="researchUrl" value="/testurl/" />
								<property name="imageRef" value="images/team-members/NH.jpg" />
							</bean>
						</list>
					</property>
				</bean>
			</list>
		</property>
	</bean>
</beans>